Guide to the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records, 1970-2012.
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records,
- Series III. Empty Closet
  - Alphabetical Subject Files 1975-2004 (Second Donation)
    - G-L
      - John, Susan, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Jones Pond, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Judicial Process Commission, c. 1993 (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - Kansas, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - Kavanaugh, Barbara, c. 1995-1999 (Box 21, Folder 27)
      - Kentucky, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Kinison, Sam, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - Kinnicutt (WHAM), 1992 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - KODAK (Lambda), 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 31)
      - Kowalski, Sharon & Karen Thompson, c. 1987-1991 (Box 21, Folder 32)
      - Kramer, Larry, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      - Labor, 1988, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 34)
      - Ladies Recreation Club, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 35)
      - Lambda Legal Defense Press Releases (1), 1989-1992 (Box 21, Folder 36)
      - Lambda Legal Defense Press Releases (2), 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 37)
      - Lambda Legal Defense Press Releases (3), 1995-1997 (Box 21, Folder 38)
      - Lambda Legal Defense Press Releases (4), 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 39)
      - Lambda Legal Defense Press Releases (5), 1998 (Box 21, Folder 40)
      - Lambda Legal Defense Press Releases (6), 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 41)
      - Lambda Legal Defense Press Releases (7), 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 42)
      - Lambda Legal Defense - Lambda Update (1), 1992-1994 (Box 21, Folder 43)
      - Lambda Legal Defense - Lambda Update (2), 1997, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 44)
      - Lambda Literary Awards, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 45)
      - Lesbian & Gay Community Services Center- New York City (1), 1987-1992 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Lesbian & Gay Community Services Center- New York City (2), 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Lambda Literary Awards, 1993-1994, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Lang, KD, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Latino/a Gays, 1993-2002 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Lawrence, Roy, Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Leather, 1990-2000 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Legal Rights, c. 1993-1999 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Legal Rights - Court Cases, c. 1987, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Legislation, Anti-Discrimination, c. 1992 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Lesbian Avengers, c. 1993-1994. 1999 (Box 22, Folder 11)
        Flyers.
      - Lesbian Living, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Lesbian Herstory Archives, 1990-2001 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Lesbian & Gay Health Network, 1988-1989, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Lesbian & Gay Health Association, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Lesbian & Gay Health & Human Services Network, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Lesbian & Gay Public Awareness Project, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Lesbian, Gay & Bisexual People in Health Science, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Lesbian/Gay Vote, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Lesbian & Gay Bands of America, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Lesbian & Gay Writers (National), c. 1989 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Lesbian Health (see Breast Cancer), 1993-1994, 1997-2000 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Lesbian Resource Center (LRC), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Lesbian Leaders, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Lesbian Planning Coalition, Undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
        Pamphlets
      - Lesbian Resource Center, 1981, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Lesbian Sexuality, 1988, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - Lesbian Studies, c. 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Lesbian Variety Show, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Lesbian Writers' Group, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - Lesbians of Color, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - Liberace, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - Libraries, 1989-1993, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - Libertarians, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - Lilac Rainbow Alliance for the Deaf, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 35)
      - Limbaugh, Rush, c. 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 36)
      - Lobbying, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 37)
      - The Loft, 2001-2003 (Box 22, Folder 38)
        Community News Newsletters
      - Lonsberry, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 39)
      - Looks-ism (gay male), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 40)
      - London Bombing, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 41)
      - Los Angeles, 1988-1996, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 42)
      - Lutherans, c. 1987-1990, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - M-S
      - McClarrie, Michael, c. 1998 (Box 22, Folder 44)
      - Magazines, c. 1992 (Box 22, Folder 45)
        Christus Omnibus premiere issue.
      - Maine, c. 1995 (Box 22, Folder 46)
      - Mains, Tim, c. 1987-1989, 2001, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 47)
      - March on Washington '79, 1979, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 48)
        Handwritten note, flyer for moving screening about the March on Washington
      - March on Washington 1987 (1), c. 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 49)
        Media workshop booklet, flyers, pamphlets.
      - March on Washington 1987 (2), c. 1987 (Box 22, Folder 50)
        Flyers, pamphlets, booklet, The Washington Blade Special Edition for the National March on Washington.
      - March on Washington 1993, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 51)
        Meeting report, Washington Blade Special Edition for the National March on Washington
      - Marijuana, Medical, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 52)
      - Marketing, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 53)
      - Community Spirit, Undated; FD-26 (Box 22, Folder 53)
      - Marketing/Fliers - Dog Sitting, Mattresses, etc., Undated (Box 22, Folder 54)
      - Marketing - Fliers/Ads, Undated (Box 22, Folder 55)
      - Marketing - Fliers for Restaurants, parties, eyeglasses stores, c. 1997 (Box 22, Folder 56)
      - Marketing - Fliers for Bars, bike shops, realtors, etc., c. 1997 (Box 22, Folder 57)
      - Marketing - Fliers, pamphlets, posters, business cards, Undated (Box 22, Folder 58)
      - Marketing - Fliers, ads, programs, quarter cards, Undated (Box 22, Folder 59)
      - Marketing - Fliers: Lawrence Kriger, lawyer for gay families, Undated (Box 22, Folder 60)
      - Marketing - Fliers, posters, Undated (Box 22, Folder 61)
      - Marriage (Canada), 2003 (Box 22, Folder 62)
      - Marriages (gay, legal), 1995-2003 (Box 22, Folder 63)
      - Marriage - News clippings, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 64)
      - Married Gays, c. 1988, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 65)
      - Martin, Cheryl Amati, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 66)
      - Maryland, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 67)
      - Matlovich, Leonard, 1975, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 68)
      - Massachusetts, c. 1988-1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
        Posters, quarter cards.
      - Mayoral Forum '93, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - McCaffery Murder, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Media - Local, 1988, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Media - National, c. 1975-1976, 1988-1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Memorial Day Parades, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Men's Movement, 1970s (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Men, Masculinity, 1988, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Men of All Colors Together, New York City (MACT) (1), 1997-2003 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Men of All Colors Together, New York City (MACT) (2), 1993-1997 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Men of All Colors Together, New York City (MACT) (3), 1993-1997 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Men of Color Health Awareness (MOCHA), 1999-2003 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Mental Health, 1976, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Merriam-Webster (Thesaurus), 1999 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Metropolitan Community Church, National (MCC) (Inc. Troy Perry), 1988-1989, 1997-1999 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Metropolitan Community Church (Open Arms MCC), Local, 1988-1995 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Methodists, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Michigan, 1987-1993 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Military (1), 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Military (2), 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Military (3), 1993-2003 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Milk, Harvey, 1985, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Millennium March, 1996-2000 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Miller-Marlboro Boycott, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Minnesota, Undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Monroe Coalition for Democracy, 1998-2001 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Monroe County Legislature, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Montana, 1995, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Montreal, 1996, 1999, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Moore, Bobby, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Moral Majority, Jerry Falwell, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Morehouse, Dr. William, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Mumia Abu Jamal, 1995, 1999, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Music (1), 1991-1997 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Music (2), 1996, 1998, 2000, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - National Association of People with AIDS, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - National Center for Lesbian Rights, 1990-1993, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - National Coalition of Black Lesbians and Gays, 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - National Coming Out Day, 1988-1993 (Box 23, Folder 39)
      - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Press Releases, August 1986-1993 (Box 23, Folder 40-47)
      - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Press Releases continued, January 1994-1999 (Box 24, Folder 1-15)
      - NGLTF Press Releases/Emails (24), 2000 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - NGLTF Press Releases/Emails (25), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - National Gay Rights Advocates, 1987-1990 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - National Lesbian and Gay Health Association, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - National Lesbian and Gay Journalists Association, 2001-2003 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - National Lesbian and Gay Law Association, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - National Lesbian Conference, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Pritchard, Bill, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Pop Against Homophobia, Undated (Box 24, Folder 52)
      - Names Project, Rochester, 1989, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Rochester AIDS (1), 1983-1998 (Box 24, Folder 25)
        Most Rochester materials, including interviews, connect to AIDS Rochester organization.
      - Rochester Background (2), 1995 (Box 24, Folder 26)
        Agenda Newsletter
      - Rochester (3), 1984-1997 (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Rochester(4), 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Rochester Interviews- Dan Bielak, May 11, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Rochester Interviews- Sue Cowell, January 19, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - Rochester Interviews- Ken Dorner, May 21, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Rochester Interviews- Mark Ellenwood, September 18, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Rochester Interviews- Tony Greene, October 3, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - Rochester Interviews- Leonard Freedman, September 18, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Rochester Interviews- Martin Hiraga, June 7, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - Rochester Interviews- Jim Ide, January 14, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - Rochester Interviews- Hazel Jeffries, September 13, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - Rochester Interviews- Jeff Kost, July 30, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 38)
      - Rochester Interviews- Tim Mains, February 12, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - Rochester Interviews- Sidney Metzger, September 13, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 40)
      - Rochester Interviews- John Noble, December 14, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 41)
      - Rochester Interviews- Bill Pritchard, July 17, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 42)
      - Rochester Interviews- Allan Richards, August 22, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - Rochester Interviews- Rodolfo Rivera, May 11, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Rochester Interviews- Elaine Smith, January 18, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 45)
      - Rochester Interviews- Bill Valenti, September 13, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 46)
      - Rochester Interviews- Mary Lou Weltz, December 14, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 47)
      - Rochester Politics- Mayoral and Council Elections (1), 1993, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 48-50)
      - Papers by Donald Rosenthal, 1990-1997 (Box 24, Folder 51)
        Dilemmas in the Development of AIDS Service Organizations in Upstate New York', 'Gay Politics, AIDS Politics in Four New York Cities', 'Culture Wars, Regime Change and Gay and Lesbian Politics in Four New York Cities'
      - Seventh Day Adventists, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Sex, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Sexual Compulsives Anonymous Newsletter, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Spitzer, Eliot, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Stewart, Dan, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Stonewall Awards, 1991-1999 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Stonewall 25, Stonewall Awards (1), 1988-1996 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Stonewall 25, Stonewall Awards (2), 1993-1996 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Stopping Anti-Gay Abuse of Students in Public Schools - Lambda Legal Defense, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 9)
        Document by David Buckel
      - Studds, Gerry E. (Representative), 1987-1995 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Gay and Lesbian Students - Conferences and demonstrations, 1990-2002 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Strassner, Mike and Baker, Michael, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 12)
        Newspaper article about first gay couple to openly attend a prom in Central New York.
      - Studies and surveys, Local - The Empty Closet, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Supreme Court: Bowers vs. Hardwick, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Supreme Court: Civil Disobedience, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Supreme Court: Gay rights rulings, 1976-1977, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Syracuse, 1987-2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
        Newsletters and letters to the mayor.
    - T-Z
      - Take Back the Night, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Teachers- New York City Lesbian and Gay Teachers Association Newsletters (1), 1985-1991 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Teachers- New York City Lesbian and Gay Teachers Association Newsletters (2), 1992-2000 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Teachers, 1975-1999 (Box 25, Folder 21)
        News clippings, Lesbian and Gay Teachers Association Newsletter, and pamphlets.
      - Team Rochester, 1994, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Television, 1988-1998 (Box 25, Folder 23)
        Press releases and news clippings.
      - Television, 1998-2003 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Temporary tattoos, Undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Tennessee, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Texas, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Theater- Local, Rochester, 1988, 1994-1995, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Theater- National, 1988-1995 (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Therapy, 1991-1993 (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Third Party: "A Call to Party" by Dan MC Donald, Undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - Third World Queer Liberation article, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - Tinky Winky, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 33)
        Gay Teletubby
      - Top Free Equality, 1988, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - Transgender, 1987-2002 (Box 25, Folder 35)
        News clippings
      - Travel (1), 1980-1997 (Box 25, Folder 36)
        Brochures.
      - Travel (2), 1998-2003 (Box 25, Folder 37)
      - Tsongas, Paul E., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        Article about the presidential candidate.
      - Umpierre, Luz Maria, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Union ceremonies, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Unions (Gays in), 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Rochester Unitarian- First Unitarian Church Newsletters (1), 1989-1994 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Rochester Unitarian- First Unitarian Church Newsletters (2), 1994-1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Rochester Unitarian- First Unitarian Church Newsletters (3), 1998-2002 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Unitarian Universalist Lesbian/Gay Concerns, 1987-1993 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - United Church Coalition for Lesbian/Gay Concerns, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - United Farm Workers, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - United Nations, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 11)
        Press release for Stonewall 25 March
      - United Way, Undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - University of Rochester, 1992, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Utah, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Utica, 1987-1989, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Vacco, Dennis, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Valenti, Bill, Undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
        Regarding his resignation as director of Community Health Network
      - Vasquez, Carmen, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 18)
        Paper entitled "Building Our House: Long-Term Planning for Building a Racially Inclusive Movement"
      - Vermont, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Veterans, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Video, 1992-1996, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Network Q Premier Membership, 1992; FD-21 (Box 26, Folder 21)
        Press Releases.
      - Network Q PR- Charter Memberships Ending, 1992; FD-22 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Network Q PR- John Topping Profile, 1992; FD-23 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Network Q PR- Santa Fe, 1992; FD-24 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Network Q PR- Palm Springs, 1992; FD-25 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Vinnie Vicki Awards, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Vote (LGBT), 2000 (Box 26, Folder 23)
        Includes report by the Gill Foundation "Out and Into the Voting Booth: Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual & Transgender Voters in 2000"
      - Warfield, Thomas, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Washington, DC, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 25)
      - Washington (state), 1992, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - White, Mel, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Wegmans Bias (Syracuse), 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 28)
      - Women Against a Violent Environment (WAVE), 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 29)
        Paper by Barbara Kasper and Carmen Aponte entitled "Women and Violence: A Rochester Area Community Survey"
      - Women & Art, 1988, 1992, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 30)
      - Women Against Pornography, c. 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 31)
      - Women's Cancer Action Project, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 32)
      - Women- Economics, 1988, 1993, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 33)
      - Women's Encampment- Seneca, 1987, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 34)
      - Women's Health Issues, 1988, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 35)
      - Women's Music, 1982-1994 (Box 26, Folder 36)
      - Women's Music (2), Undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
        Primarily photographs.
      - Women- New York State, 1988, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 38)
        Legislative Women's Caucus of NY State 1988, National Park Service Women's Equality Celebration 1990.
      - Women's Peace Movement, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 39)
      - Women & Religion, 1988, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 40)
      - Women's Rights, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 41)
        Press packet for Women's Equality Day 1995.
      - Women's Studies, 1988-1989, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 42)
      - Women- Violence Against, 1990-1992, 1995, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 43)
      - Workplace- Out in, 1995, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 44)
      - Workers World Party, 1988, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 45)
      - Working Assets, 1986-1988 (Box 26, Folder 46)
      - WTO Protests, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 47)
      - World Wide Web, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 48)
      - Writers, 1989-1996, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 49)
      - Yacknin, Ellen, 2000-2002 (Box 26, Folder 50)
      - Youth, 1988-2001 (Box 26, Folder 51)
        1993 Education Report "Making Schools Safe for Gay and Lesbian Youth"
      - Youth (Local), 1993, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Alphabetical Photograph File (incomplete)
    - Freedom Singers, Undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Friedrich, Sue, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Frontrunners, Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Fundraisers, Undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Gayla, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      8th Annual Holiday Gala at Strong Museum. Pictures L-R- Andrea Segmond and Ellen Yacken. Photo by Doug Meszler
    - March on Washington, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Martin, Cindy, Undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Massachusetts, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      Ray Drew being stomped by security guard at Massachusetts State House during demo to protest stalling of gay rights bill, Boston, Jan.4, 1988.
    - Matlovich, Leonard, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - McNaught, Brian, Undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - McNeil, Rev. John, Undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Meet Your Community, Undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
      Chuck Collins, Breda
    - Memorial Day Parades, c. 1986, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Men's Music, Undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Meszler, Doug, Undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Metropolitan Community Church, Undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Milk, Harvey, Undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Millennium March- DC, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Misc. Protest, c. 1986-1991 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Miss Gay Rochester (1), 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Miss Gay Rochester (2), 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Miss Gay Rochester (3), 2000 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - MOCHA Project, c. 2000 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Monacelli, Harry, Undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Monroe Community College- Diversity Day, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Moquin, Bruce, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Moran, Kitty, Undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Mosher, Ray, Undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Music, c. 1996, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Nabozny, Jamie, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 30)
      Tzabaco Catalog Lesbian and Gay Community fund $25,000 award presentation to GLSTN.
    - Nader, Ralph, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - NAMES Project, c. 1987-1992 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - NAMES Quilt/ ACT-UP in D.C., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - National Lesbian Conference, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - National Organization of Women (NOW), Undated (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - National Women's Rights Historical Park, Undated (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Natoli-Rombach, Richard, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Nazareth College, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 38)
      Graffiti incident and candlelight rally
    - Nesbitt, Ellen, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Night of 100 Parties (1), 1994 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Night of 100 Parties (2), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU), 1990 (Box 27, Folder 42)
      1990 Legislative Voting Record Index.
    - NYC Pride, c. 2000 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - New York State Lesbian & Gay Lobby, c. 1986, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - New York State Lesbian & Gay Lobby March- Albany, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - New York State Officials, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 46)
      Virginia Apuzzo, Bichard Burns, Governor Mario Cuomo
    - Nudd, Jacki, c. 1983 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - O'Brien, Jim, Undated (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Out & About, c. 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Out & Equal, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Owens, Bob, Undated (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Pape, Paul, c. 1997, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Parade & Picnic, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Picnic- Rochester Gay Community, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Piersol, Dr. Charles, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Pink Flamingos & Purple Hearts Convention, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Plunkett, Susan, 1986, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Political Caucus, 1992-1995 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Politicians, c. 1986-1989 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Poets (local), Undated (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Pratt, Minnie Bruce, Undated (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - Price, Deb, c. 1995 (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Misc. Photographs (1), Undated (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Misc. Photographs (2), Undated (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - Unlabelled Photographs and Negatives, Undated (Box 27, Folder 65)
    - Parkleigh Advertisement Photograph, Undated (Box 27, Folder 66)
    - Art for Advertisements, c. 1999-2002 (Box 31, Folder 19-26,28-29)
    - Freetime Graphix 4 - Graphics Files, Undated; ZD-10 (Box 31)
      Found with Art for Advertisements
    - Empty Closet 40th Anniversary materials, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 27)
      Marked "Library Archives"
    - Empty Closet 1971-2010, c. 2010; DVD-1197 (Box 31)
    - Empty Closet March Issue, Undated; CD-2207 (Box 31)
      Photos by Doug Meszler
    - Empty Closet October, Undated; CD-2208 (Box 31)
    - Empty Closet, November 2004; Folder 28 (Box 31)
  - Back Issues on Microfilm
    - Empty Closet, January 1971-December 1978 (Reel 1)
    - Empty Closet, January 1979-August 1984 (Reel 2)